Guide to the St. Thomas More Editorial Project, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- University Library. St. Thomas More Editorial Project, 1958-1994; Accession 1997-A-025
  - Shanahan, Msgr. Daniel, 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Shapiro, Harold I., 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Short, Bryan C., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Shepley, John, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Sherwood, E.A., 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Simons, Dr. Jos., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Smelzer, Marshall, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Smyser, H.M., 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Society of Antiquaries, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Specter, S., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Stechert-Hafner, Inc. Booksellers, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Stevenson, Mrs. T.H., December 1, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Strauss, Albrecht, 1969-1974 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Sullivan, Dr. S., 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Susman, Steve, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Stone, George W., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Taft, Arthur I., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Tanis, James, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Thomson, Fred, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Thompson, Earl, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Thomson, C.F.L., Chelsea Old Church, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - T. Hought, 1960-1962 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Thran, Sally; Ave Maria, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Tours, Renaissance Center, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Tracy, Robert, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Traister, Barbara, recommendation, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Trout, Philip H., Virginia, More genealogy, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Tully, R.E., 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - University microfilms, 1962-1969 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - L'Utopiè, Brussells, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Vallez, Janine, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Vieth, D.M., 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Vivien, Sister M., O.P.; Caldwell College, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Walpole project, history, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Walz, Herman J., 1963 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - West, Soren P., 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Whiteman, Harold B.; faculty freshman advising, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Wilson, Prof. F.P., 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Wilson, Mr. Thomas J., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Wimsatt, W.K., 1960-1971 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Wing, Donald, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Winks, Robin W., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Wolfe, Prof. B., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Wolf, T.E., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Wood, J.L., British Museum, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Wuerttembergische Landesbibliothek, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Wyman, Peter M., July 27, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Yale press, order department, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Young, Richard B., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Zeeveld, Professor W. Gordon, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Zerrad, E., December 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Mortimer Levine, archives, 1969-1977 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Lievsay, John L., April 18, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Logan, George M., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Laughran, Hugh L., January 17, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Lusardi dissertation (Barnes-More), 1963 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Macek, Robert C., May 26, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - MacLure, Millar, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Mahoney, Edward P., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Sister scholastica, correspondence, 1962-1978 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Sr. Scholastica, 1961-1972 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Manley, CW12, correspondence, PL problems, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Manley correspondence with E.D. Coffin, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Manley, Frank (parts 1 and 2), 1964-1978 (Box 8, Folder 107-108)
  - Marc'hadour, letters, August-September '77 with notes and corrections, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Marcus, Ruth; Wall Street Journal, June 9, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Margolin, Jean-Claude, 1970-1978 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Marc'hadour, G. (parts 1 and 2), May 1974 (Box 8, Folder 112-113)
  - Marston, T., Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Martz, Louis L., 1962-1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - McConica, recommendation, July 1, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - McCutcheon, Elizabeth, April 18, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - McInerney, Murray V., Australia, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - McLean, A., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - McNamara, Joseph S., October 31, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - McShane, Rev. Edward, S.J., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Marivs, Heresies, May 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Medine, Peter E., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Metzdorf, Robert F., December 4, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Metzner, Patricia, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Michigan University, English department publications, August 11, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Miles, Leland, 1963-1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Miller recommendation, 1968, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Mosaic, November 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Miller, 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Mosaic, November 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Murphy, Clare M., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Murray, Francis, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Nagy, Laszlo; Hungary, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Nakamura, Toru, March 15, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Nakano, Yasuo, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Nash, Ray, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - National Portrait Gallery, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Nauert, Prof. Charles G., Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Ney, Marie, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Nichols, Fred J., October 29, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Nichols, Fred; Neo-Latin, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Brother Thomas More Dias Neto OSB, January 31, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Nuetzel Machinary Co., M.E. Stringer, February 14, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Oakley, Frank, August 14, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - McGugan, Prof. Ruth, 1972-1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - O'Donnell, James J., May 24, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - O'Donnell, Mary Ann, literary research newsletter, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - O'Kelly, Bernard, 1961-1974 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Olin, John C., Fordham, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Fordham, February 10-11, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Ong, Walter J.S.J., 1958-1977 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Parks, Prof. G.B., 1961-1977 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Patrick, Prof. J. May, 1959-1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Pelikan, Dean Jaroslav, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Phillips, Margaret M., 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Pineas, Dr. Rainer, Pace College, 1958-1965 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Prescott, Anne, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Prévost, A., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Rabkin, Norman, March 17, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Radice, Betty, October 29, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Reedijk, Dr. C., 1958-1970 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Rendel, George, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Renaissance news, 1958-1978 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - RETS, position papers, requests, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - RETS, MLA, requests for position paper, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - RETS, Chicago, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Reynolds, E.E., 1959-1977 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Robert, Brother S., St. Mary's, California, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Robinson, Fred, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Rogers, D.M., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Rothschild, Herbert B., Jr., January 12, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Ruland, Richard, November 1, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Russell, Father, More House, November 18, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Ryan, Mr. G., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - St. Peter, George M., January 22, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Seaman, Angela, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Savoie, Upton A., Jr., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Scarisbrick, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Schaeffer, John D., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Schneebeli, Robert; Dr. Phil, April 22, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Schuster, Louis A., 1960-1975 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Seitz, Howard, March 8, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Shenker, Isael; N.Y. Times, June 9, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Shillingsburg, Peter, coordinator, CSE, January 10, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Singh, Jaswant,librarian, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Slavin, Arthur, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Smith, Constance, 1964-1978 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Smith, David R., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Smith, Norine J., 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Sodeman, W.J., April 10, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Spitz, L., 1965-1977 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Stanley, Eric, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Stringer, Gary, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Suzuki, Yoshinori, March 29, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Sylvester, correspondence to project, 1965, April-May 1977 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Tamura, Hideo, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Thomas, Alan G.; antequarian bookseller, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Thompson, Craig, Lucian, 1969-1978 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Thompson, Professor Craig R., 1958-1978 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Thornhill, E.A., May 25, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Tollers, Vincent L.; literature research newsletter, January 24, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Tomlinson, G.A., April 21, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Trapp, Warburg Institute, 1958-1978 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Tromly, Frederic B., 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Tsukada, Tomiharu, Ph.D, April 10, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Tucker, Melvin J., 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Watanabe, Yoshiko, May 2, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Tucker, Thomas R., March 24, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Turner, Keith, attorney, February 1, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Heerhoven, G. Van den, March 10, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Vincitorio, G., 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Visitation Academy, St. Louis, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Waith, Eugene M., 1964-1978 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Wall, John N. (Homilies), 1976 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Warren, James P., Auburn, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Watkins, D.R., 1961-1978 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Webber, Joan, November 14, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Wood, Charles T., Dartmouth, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Wooden, Warren W., 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Yeskoo, Richard, Undated (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Yale press, Cavendish, 1960-1977 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Yale press, contracts, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Yale press, publicity, 1961-1966 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Young, Archibald, research on More's use of Dialogue, 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Alkire, J., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Allen and Unwin Ltd. more biography, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Alton, R.E., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Angero conference, April 1965 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Archives stationary, Undated (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Arundel, M.S., August 1962 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Barber, H., November 1974 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Bartlett, Kenneth, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Berthelet, Wilfong prospectus, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Biblioteque National, more holdings, Undated (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Blackford, Paul W., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Brown lecture, November 18, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Brown lecture, April 1967 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Brown University Library and Carter Brown Library, 1959, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Brussells exhibition, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Bursary Boy, 1961-1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Bursary boy, 1958-1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cambridge University press, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cast, David, 1971-1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Commission, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Catholic transcript, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Centenary, April 6-9, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Chicago, University of; librarian, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Clogan, Paul; Medievalia et Humanistica 6, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Cole, Douglas, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Computers, Shakespeare, MND, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Academy of Arts and Sciences, Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Cook, Dr. Charles; Pediatrics, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University press, Conti Translation and Giraldi, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Cousins, Tony; Australia, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Culler, D., 1971-1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Cummings Publishing Co., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Daly, James J., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Daly, S.J., L.J. (Rev.), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Davis, Natalie (Brown), 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Debenham, W.S., April 24, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Delgado, J.J., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Detachment and involvement, More; Gleeson lecture, San Francisco, Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - St. John's, April 10, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Dobson, E.J., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Duke University Press, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Involvement and Detachment in the World of Thomas More, February 7, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Editing Thomas More, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Emerson, W., NEH, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Emery, Ruth, 1970-1978 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Engelberg, Edward, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Antiquariaat, Erasmus, 1959-1962 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Esmond, Margaret Powell, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Etudes Augustiniennes, 1973-1982 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Everett and Edwards, cassettes, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Flegel, Kenneth M., M.D., 1974 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Fleming, R.B. and Co. Ltd., Africa house, Kingsway, london, W.C.Z., 1958-1967 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Folger, John Andrews, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Folger, Megan Lloyd, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Folger library, June 1961, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Folger lecture, October 1969 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Folger, Editor, March 25, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Folger, Editorial Brand, October 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Folger, editorial committee, March 24, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Folger, October 6, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Folger, editorial committee, October 5, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Folger committee, May 9-10, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Folger, minutes, editorial committee meeting, December 5, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Folger seminar, February 7, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Folger, newsletter, etc..., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Folger, Sylvester-Mellor lecture, December 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Foster, Ruel E., April 19, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Foxon, David, British Museum, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Fraser, Russell, 1970, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - J.R. Freeman and Company, microfilming, July 24, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Howell, Mrs. Henry W., Frick Museum, 1961, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Frost lecture, Angers, April 1965 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Frost lecture, Angers, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Fulop, R.E., May 9, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Gleeson Library, University of San Francisco, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Gleeson lecture, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Greene, Tom, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Greenslade, S.L., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Hardison, O.B., Renaissance Institute, 1969-1976 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Harner, James L., March 27, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Harrier, R.C., N.Y.U., 1967-1975 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Harris, Paul T., 1966 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Hartman, Geoffrey, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Harvard University press, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Harvard University press, Surtz, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Harvey, Gabriel; Notes on Gascoigne, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Hay, comments on paper, April 2, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Heninger, S.K., June 25, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Hieatt, Kent, West Ontario, March 7, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Hill, W. Speed, Hooker edition, 1968-1977 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - House, University mortgage, October 13, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Huber, Elizabeth A., April 9, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Huntington library quarterly, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Jaros, Oliver J., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Jarrott, Catherine, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Kaufmann, R.J., Texas, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Kelly, Henry A., UCLA, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Kent, George O., Library of Congress, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Studies in English literature, Kincaid article, Richard III, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Kinsley, James, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Kirkpatrick, Robert L., Rhodes, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Knachel, Philip A. (Folger), 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Knights, L.C., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Kozicki, Henry, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Kroczewski, J., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Kuttner, Stephen, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Lake Hayward, directions, Undated (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Lambeth, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Libraries, letter of introduction for graduate students, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Liebert, Herman W., 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Louvain, Latin conference, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Lyons, Leonard, Jr., 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Mack, M., 1965-1976 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Makinson, Albert, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Manhattan College, lecture, Brother Paul Gladhill file, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Manuscript Society, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Martz, Dialogue of Comfort article, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Martz, "Family", 1959 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - McFadden, H.P., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - McNamee, M.B., S.J., 1964-1976 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Meade, Peter; British Museum, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Medievalia and Humanistica, 1971-1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Meyer, Carl S.; Concordia, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Charles A., Lake Forest, Illlinois, November 8, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Modern Language Quarterly, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Montgomery, R.L., Texas studies, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Moore, Thelma, genealogy, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Thomas More Society, N.Y.C., May 27, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - J. Pierpont Morgan Library, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Morris, Brian; Sheffield, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Newberry Library, Chicago, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Newns, Brian; Venerable Collegio Iinglese, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - State University of New York press, Albany; Norman S. Mongouni, director, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - University of North Carolina, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Novarr, David, 1960, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Ohio University Press, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - O'Malley, John W., S.J., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Parker, Douglas H. (Canada), 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Parks, S.R., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Patience, source, Miss Borroff, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Persse, Mrs. John, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Petti, Anthony G., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Phialas, Pete, Chapel Hill, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - C.W. Post College, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Pratt, Dana J., Y.U.P., 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Price, Martin, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Princeton University Press, 1964-1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - PMLA, articles read, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Racin, John, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Rastell, books printed by, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Reader's Encyclopedia, Crowell, Johnson, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Renaissance texts, MLA, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Another G.C. Richards letter, March 28, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Richardson, W.C., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Rogers, E.F., correspondence to [includes photographs], 1964 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Rogers, permission to use Allen, 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Roger B. Rollin, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Rowe, Donald F., S.J.; Loyola Art Gallery, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Royal Historical Society, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Rustle and Rustle, June 1965 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - M. Paton Ryan, R.S.M., 1965-1973 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - St. Peter, George M., 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Sister M. Samuel, O.P., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Schlesinger, Bruno P., 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Scott-Craig, T.S.K., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Schoene, Miss Mary P., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Seeber, Hans Ulrich, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Selestat Library, Germany, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Schoeck, outline for Laterin council study, essays etc..., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Secretarial applications, 1958-1978 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Coffin, Elizabeth, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Seymour, M.C., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Shakespeare, old spelling addition, 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Shapiro, Harold, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Shapiro, I.A., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Shaw, Robert B., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Sherbo, Arthur, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Southern, R.W., 1974 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Sowards, J.K., Wichita University, 1959-1970 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Stanford University Library, Cavendish, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Stegmann, André; tours institute, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Sullivan, Patrick J., 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Talbert, E.W.; University of North Carolina, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Taylor, Charles; provost, January 2, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Tetel, Marcel, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Texas Studies in Literature and Language, September 19, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Thompson, shoestring reprint, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Thorpe, James; Huntington Library, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Toronto lecture, editiing Thomas More, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Toronto University press, ERASMUS, 1969-1977 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Toronto, Waller manuscript, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Toronto, Kincaid manuscript, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Toronto, editorial conference, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Trapp, Expositio article, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Travel, December 26-29, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Trinity College, Cambridge, England, December 2, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Tyne, Rev. James, S.J., 1964-1969 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Utopia, Western Virginia lecture, Undated (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Vatican Library, February 16, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Villa Madonna, Thomas More College, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Richard Gibeaux, Villa Madonna, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Vincitorio, December 6, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Vogelgesang, John, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Vrooman, Yale library, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Weinstein, Minna F., August 8, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Welcher, Jeanne; Utopia, imaginary voyage seminar, MLA, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - World book encyclopedia, 1968-1977 (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Heuer, Prof. H., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Hoffman, Prof. Ross, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Hogan, Miss Mary C., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Horne, David (part 1 and 2), 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 108-109)
  - Horner, Ruth, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Hotson, Leslie, June 15, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Houghton, Arthur A., January 19, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Hughes, Philip, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Huttar, Charles A., Gordon College, October 11, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Immaculate, Sr. Clare, December 24, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Institute de Recherche, Paris, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Irons, Richard K., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Itrat-Husain, Prof., October 2, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - M. L'abbé Jules Jacques, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - James, Barbara, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - James, David, January 1971 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Jobes, Gertrude, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Jones, Judith P., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Jordan, Thomas F., University of San Francisco, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Joseph, Sr. Gertrude, CSJO, Downey California, 1958-1964 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Judd, Mrs. F.M., more prints, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Judd, J. M., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Kathleen, Sister Mary, G.N.S.H., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Abstractions and Experience, A.N. Kaul, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Kellogg, David, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Kendall, Paul, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - P.J. Kenedy and sons, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Kenefick, Gordon, June 13, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Kenny, A., Undated (Box 11, Folder 136)